Thaddeus W. Maliszewski collection CPAA 86.04
Connecticut Polish American Archives, Elihu Burritt Library, Central Connecticut State University
- Democratic Party, Professional Assignments, Jobs
  - Election for Probate Judge in Windsor, Conn.- (TWM running) Newspaper clippings, maps, charts, correspondence, campaign materials, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Election for Probate Judge in Windsor, Conn.- Financial documents, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Election for Probate Judge in Windsor, Conn.- Leaflets, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Ella Grasso campaign- Correspondence, clippings, statements, poll, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Eva Hudak's bid for Board of Education- Clippings, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1978 Probate elections- (TWM vs. Walter Russell) Fundraising documents, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1978 Probate elections- Workers, organization, time table on election day. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1978 Probate elections- Caucus speech (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1978 Probate elections- Publicity, speech (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1978 Probate elections- Newspaper clippings, advertisements, correspondence. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 1978 Probate elections- Endorsements of TWM (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 1978 Probate elections- Slander- Correspondence, newspaper clippings. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 1978 Probate elections- Cases, Russell's mistakes (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 1978 Probate elections- Issues, probate law, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Arbitrator for the State of Connecticut (TWM), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - U.S. Senatorial Campaign- Dodd, Christopher J., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - TWM- Appointments to U.S. major, 1959; Lieutenant Colonel, 1963, 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - TWM- Military service and justice, 1957-1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - TWM- Military service- Related identification and training documents, performance reports, promotions, 1947-1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - TWM– Retirement; things to do; general information, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - TWM- Judge Advocate General's School US Army- Courses, completion notifications, correspondence, course catalogs, 1955-1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - TWM- Military service & Connecticut Judge Advocate Guard service- Service records, correspondence, medical records, 1955-1959 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - TWM- Army Reserve Records- Correspondence, pay records, records jacket, 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Reunion of 17 Communication Squadron- Roster, correspondence, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Military Staff, Connecticut- Governor William O'Neill, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Military Staff, Connecticut- Governor Ella Grasso, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - “Constitutional law - Freedom of speech- Power of a Municipality to Regulate the use of Sound Trucks,”by TWM., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - “Classified Digest of Proposals Introduced in the Connecticut General Assembly of 1949” [prepared by TWM] (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut Supreme Court cases handled by TWM, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Supreme Court cases handled by TWM, 1961-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Windsor Municipal Court, 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Endorsements for TWM's appointment to Connecticut Court of Common Pleas, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Hartford County Bar Association- Membership lists, 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Hartford County Bar Association- TWM's committee work, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut Bar Association- Bench-Bar Committee- Minutes, correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - University of Connecticut Law School Alumni Association- Correspondence, minutes, 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - YMCA Hartford Friends of Boys Alumni- 50th Anniversary- Programs, expenses, lists, 1980-1992 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - American Red Cross, Windsor Chapter- Correspondence, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission of Windsor, CT- Minutes, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Polish aliens and INS in CT- Clippings, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - PAC, CT- Campaign against INS [Polish aliens] correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Winslow Automatics vs. INS- Court documents, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Windsor Municipal elections, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Judiciary- Miscellaneous notes, newspaper clippings, laws, 1957-1959 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- American Council of Polish Cultural Clubs (ACPCC, later ACPC)
  - American Council of Polish Cultural Clubs (ACPC) - Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - ACPC- Committees, Introductory Pamphlet, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - ACPC- Young Americans of Polish Descent (YAPD)- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - ACPC- Board Meeting- Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - ACPC- Executive Board Meeting- South Bend, Indiana, April 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - ACPC- Executive Board Meeting- Hartford, Connecticut, August 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - ACPC- Board of Directors Meeting- St. Louis, November 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - ACPC- Board of Directors Meeting- Youngstown, Ohio, March 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - ACPC- Board of Directors Meeting- Bethesda, Maryland, November 3, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - ACPC- Board of Directors Meeting- Detroit, Michigan, March 30, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - ACPC- Board of Directors Meeting- Stamford, Connecticut, October 12-14, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - ACPC- Executive Board Meeting- San Francisco, California, July 1990 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - ACPC- Executive Board Meeting- Minneapolis, Minnesota, April 1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - ACPC- Board of Directors Meeting- Washington D.C., November 1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - ACPC- Board of Directors Meeting- Clearwater, Florida, March 1992 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - ACPC- Board of Directors Meeting- Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, October 1992 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - ACPC- Convention- Buffalo, New York, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - ACPC- Convention- Cambridge Springs, Pennsylvania, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - ACPC- Convention- Ypsilanti, Michigan, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - ACPC- Convention- Hartford, Connecticut, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - ACPC- Convention- Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - ACPC- Convention- San Francisco, California, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - ACPC- Convention- Pultusk, Poland, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - ACPC- Convention- Washington D.C., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Polish American Cultural Center (Philadelphia) and Polish American Social Services – Flyers, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - 50th Anniversary International Congress- Polish Institute of Arts & Sciences of America (PIASA), Yale University, June 18-29, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - ACPC- Polonaise Ball, San Francisco, November 3, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - ACPC- List of affiliated clubs, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - ACPC- President's Newsletter, 1987-1992 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - ACPC- Constitution Committee- Constitution and by-laws, correspondence, notes, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - ACPC- Membership Committee- Correspondence, reports, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - ACPC- Washington Project (Polish Cultural Center)-Washington, D.C.- Brochures, notes, donation information, fundraising, 1987-1991 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - ACPC- “Champions of Polish Heritage” award, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Catalogs from auctions from Polish art and antiques by The Lippert Gallery (New Jersey), 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - 67 Clippings, correspondence, programs- Miscellaneous, 1986-1992 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Polish Cultural Society of Palm Beaches (PSCPB) and Other Organizations
  - Photo of General Bor-Komorowski during his visit in Connecticut, June 5, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - The Polish Cultural Society of Palm Beaches (PCSPB) Articles of Incorporation & By-Laws, correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - PCSPB– Programs, clippings, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - PCSPB– Scattered issues of bulletin and activities, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - PCSPB– Correspondence, activities, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - PCSPB– Correspondence, activities, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - PCSPB– Correspondence, activities, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - PCSPB– Correspondence, activities, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - President Ronald Reagan, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Poland’s Millennium Commemorative US Postage stamps, July 30, 1966 and banquet program (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - National Advocates Society– Directory of lawyers, TWM membership, bulletins, correspondence, 1961-1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Judge T. Maliszewski Windsor Municipal Court, 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - “The Polish Way” by Adam Zamoyski – Promotion and sales, lectures, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Polish Cultural Society of Palm Beaches – Distributions of Trilogy of Henryk Sienkiewicz, translated by Z. Kuniczak, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Alan Kogosowski– Polish pianist, 1981-1986; 2000-2002, Bulk, 1981-1986; 1981-2002 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Schmidt libel controversy, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Anthony Bai vs. the Polish Cultural Society of the Palm Beaches controversy, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Walter Rekuc vs. the Polish Cultural Society of the Palm Beaches controversy, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - T.W. Maliszewski – Personal notes and clippings on Poles in World War II, 1939-1940; 1993-1999 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Polish stamps and commemorative envelopes, Bulk, 1966-1988; 1938-1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 200th Anniversary of the Polish Constitution – Flyers, clippings, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Polish-Jewish relations– Kielce Program clippings, 1987-1998 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Jedwabne controversy clippings, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Lech Walesa’s visit in the US and the opening of the Kosciuszko Chair at the University of Virginia, October 1998 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Pope John Paul II clippings, 1985-2005 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Clippings on Connecticut Polonia, CCSU, 1986-2001 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Polish-American institutions- Clippings, programs, correspondence, 1988-2002 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - “Katyn” publication by Jan Abramski and Ryszard Zywiecki (photocopy), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Polish Americans- clippings, 1978-2002 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - TWM papers- The Pulaski Legion of American-Polish Veterans and Auxiliary of Lake Worth, Inc.- Constitution and by-laws, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - TWM papers- The Pulaski Legion of American-Polish Veterans and Auxiliary of Lake Worth, Inc.- Articles of Incorporation, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - TWM papers- The Pulaski Legion of American-Polish Veterans and Auxiliary of Lake Worth, Inc.- Correspondence, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - TWM papers- The Pulaski Legion of American-Polish Veterans and Auxiliary of Lake Worth, Inc.- Membership list, blank stationary, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - TWM papers- The Pulaski Legion of American-Polish Veterans and Auxiliary of Lake Worth, Inc.- Bulletin, 1999-2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - TWM papers- Anthony S. Ostrowski- Application for veteran’s benefits and related documents, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - TWM papers- Casimir Pulaski- Monument, reinternment fort- Clippings, photographs, letters, brochures, 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - TWM papers- The Pulaski Legion of American-Polish Veterans and Auxiliary of Lake Worth, Inc. & other organizations- Polish heritage celebrations, 1993-2002 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - TWM papers- Joseph Maciejko application for veteran’s benefits and related correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - TWM papers- Pulaski Banner- Short history, photograph, clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)